womenfitness.net 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy : Women Fitness

### This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for [ www.womenfitness.net](http://www.womenfitness.net/)

### This web site has agreed to notify you of:

  1. ### What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site.

  2. ### The organization collecting the information.

  3. ### How the information is used.

  4. ### With whom the information may be shared.

  5. ### What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

  6. ### The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Women Fitness control.

  7. ### How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first Contact **** Namita Nayyar CEO Women Fitness

### Information Collection and Use 

### Company Women Fitness is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  Company Women Fitness collects information from our users at several different points on our website.  

### Registration:  

###  In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form.  During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address).  This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.  It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

### Order:

###  We request information from the user on our order form.  Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).  This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.  

###  Third Party Advertising:  

### We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  

###  Third Party Cookies:

###  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

###  Cookies: 

###  A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.  For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.  The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.  For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.   

### Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.   

###  Log Files:

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  

### Sharing:

###  We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.   

### We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.   

### We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.   

### These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  

### Links:

###  This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Women Fitness is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  

### Newsletter:

###  If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.  

###  Surveys & Contests:

### From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests.  Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).  Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.  Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.  

### Tell-A-Friend:

### If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Women Fitness will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Women Fitness stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.  The friend may contact Women Fitness to request the removal of this information from their database.  

### Security:

### This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.  When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.  

### When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. This facility is available with our channel partners 2Checkout.com.  

###  Women Fitness provides Encrypted Online Payment Transactions on SSL Secure 56 Bit platform (Industry Standard) by '2CheckOut.com Inc. (Ohio, USA)' our Credit Card Processing Company. 2Checkout.com Inc meets all BBBOnLine Reliability participation and Better Business Bureau membership standards and is authorized to display the BBBOnLine Reliability seal.

### While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.  All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk.  When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information.  Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.  Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

### If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can  Contact Us  

### Supplementation of Information  
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.  

### Special Offers:

### We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

### Site and Service Updates:

### We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.   

### Correction/Updating Personal Information:

### If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us.  This can usually be done at the member information page **** or by emailing our Customer Support **.  
 **

### Choice/Opt-out:

### Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information.  For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. You can  Contact Us for such request.  

###  Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications. You can   Contact Us for such request.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties.  We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

###  Refund Policy:

###  As our Fitness Program is a combined product compromising of access to member's area of Women Fitness's site and Personal Diet & Exercising Program. Hence, once you have made the payment and your username and password has been issued to you via email, no refund requests shall be entertained, as you have been provided access to member's area of Women Fitness's Website.  

### Notification of Changes:

### If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

  * ### Legal Statement

### Womenfitness maintains this Internet site as a service to the Internet community. The content (images and text) is the property of Womenfitness. You may download the content only for your personal, non-commercial use. The content may not be otherwise copied and/or modified.  

### Womenfitness will use reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information, but makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy or completeness. Womenfitness shall not be liable for damages of any kind arising out of your access or inability to access an Womenfitness maintained Web site or your reliance on the information contained within the Web site.  

### Womenfitness requests personal information when you sign up for our services, including your name, email address, and other information in order to provide you with a personalized program. We will not disclose any of your personal information unless you authorize us to do so, the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Womenfitness.  

### Any non-personal information, communications or material you send to Womenfitness by Internet electronic mail are on a nonconfidential basis. We are free to use and reproduce any such information freely, and for any purpose whatsoever. Specifically, we will be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose, including developing, manufacturing or marketing products. Any information you send to Womenfitness  must be truthful, legal, and not violate the rights of others. 

  * ### How to Reach Us

### **Please relay any questions you may have pertaining to our above stated policies to our Customer Service Department 314/381-6141, orContact Us.**
